<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!--$Revision: 871 $-->
<addon id="script.game.tetris" name="Tetris"
       version="1.0.2" date="11.10.2010"
       provider-name="Asteron (asteron.projects.googlepages.com)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
             library="default.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary>Tetris Game for XBMC</summary>
    <disclaimer>Remember, High-scores on-line not working....</disclaimer>
    <description>All credits and special thanks to Asteron.
Intro:
  Tetris: The timeless classic finally reaches the XBMC platform! 
  If you aren't familiar with this game by now then there's no hope for you.  
  Clear lines to get points.  Advance through the levels for large bonuses.  
  Take a chance and go for the 4-line clears to get the best score!  
  
  Are you up to the challenge?

You can find the latest version of this script at:  
  http://code.google.com/p/xbmc-scripting/
  http://asteron.projects.googlepages.com/
  
Features:
  Online and Local Highscores - submit your best scores to the online database run by Rockstarr
  Ghost Piece - turn on this advanced option from the pause menu to see where a piece will fall
  Saved settings - you will only need to enter your name once but can change it later
  Custom sounds and graphics !

Controls: 
  Left     - move piece left
  Right    - move piece right
  X        - rotate piece counter clockwise
  B / Q    - rotate piece clockwise (Q = Queue Item)
  Up       - 'near' drop : drops the piece to just above the ground
  A / Down - 'hard' drop : drops the piece to the ground and locks it
  RTrigger - increases gravity
  Start    - Pause screen

Scoring:
  1-line clear -  1 point  times current level
  2-line clear -  4 points times current level
  3-line clear -  9 points times current level
  4-line clear - 16 points times current level
  Level Up     - 15 points times new level 

Speed:
  Each level speed increases by 40% up to a maximum speed around level 8.  
  Surviving becomes very difficult and you should try to get as many points 
  as you can before losing control.

High-score Strategy:
  Going for nothing but 4-line clears will give you the most points in any 
given level.  However, this tends to lead to high towers and is inherently 
risky.  Leveling up is   easier with smaller clears and will get you more 
quickly to the higher scoring levels.  You must find a good balance between 
high-scoring multi-line clears and the smaller, safer clears.
</description>
<genre>gaming</genre>
  </extension>
</addon>
